<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>CARBEXC</title>
    <link href="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc" />
    <updated>2022-01-05T10:34:20+02:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Kristof</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Carbon Certificates</title>
        <author>
            <name>Kristof</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/carbon-certification.html"/>
        <id>https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/carbon-certification.html</id>

        <updated>2021-12-31T14:57:06+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    There is no distinction between reducing emissions with 1 tCO2e vs a removing 1 tCO2e from the atmosphere. Carbon carbon removal is more important and more difficult. They require technology. The best technology for carbon removal projects is nature - reforesting mangrove habitats, planting hemp,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">There is no distinction between reducing emissions with 1 tCO2e vs a removing 1 tCO2e from the atmosphere.</span></i></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Carbon carbon removal is more important and more difficult. They require technology. The best technology for carbon removal projects is nature - reforesting mangrove habitats, planting hemp, etc.</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">That's why we created a Carbon Removal Certification Program.</span></p>
<p><strong>CERTIFICATION</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Providing legitimacy, trading liquidity and funding opportunities to carbon removal projects.</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Carbon Removal projects are strenuous for suppliers to deliver. They are scarce and overlooked because </span></i><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">of</span></i><i><span style="font-weight: 400;"> their relative difficulty.</span></i></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Our certification methodology is being developed with transparency, accuracy and the latest technologies, with a global registry on the blockchain.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">We offer project developers or farmers project and land tracking via their phone, including land use rights, project documentation, detailed budget, independent third party validation by an accredited auditor (such as Tüv for example).</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Buyers has access to the aggregated data, IoT metrics, satellite and drone imagery.</span></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Problem With Current Carbon Credit Solutions</title>
        <author>
            <name>Kristof</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/why-existing-carbon-credit-solutions-dont-cut-it.html"/>
        <id>https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/why-existing-carbon-credit-solutions-dont-cut-it.html</id>

        <updated>2021-12-31T16:21:42+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Demand for carbon credits has been increasing year-over-year as more than 1600 companies have committed to Net Zero, of which 20% are part of the 2000 largest companies worldwide, with a $14T market cap. If you add to that the fact that 1.6 GtCO2e residual&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Demand for carbon credits has been increasing year-over-year as more than 1600 companies have committed to Net Zero, of which 20% are part of the 2000 largest companies worldwide, with a $14T market cap.</p>
<p>If you add to that the fact that 1.6 GtCO2e residual emissions need to be removed from the atmosphere, you would think that there is a plan and that there are some great solutions out there for us to get there.</p>
<p class="msg msg--highlight ">The reality could not be further from the truth, here is why.</p>
<p><strong>The current solutions for carbon credits are focused on offsetting over removal.</strong></p>
<p>When it comes to reaching net zero, one major issue is that carbon removal is sometimes mistaken or conflated with carbon offsetting. In actuality, carbon offsetting and carbon removal provide two very distinct outcomes. When one metric tonne of CO2 is emitted, another metric tonne of CO2 is prevented somewhere else, resulting in a net increase in CO2 emissions. When one metric tonne of CO2 is released, one metric tonne is totally removed from the atmosphere by carbon removal.</p>
<p>According to the <a href="https://www.iif.com/tsvcm/">Taskforce on Scaling Voluntary Carbon Markets</a>, 2 gigatons of carbon reduction is required by 2030. To achieve this we will need a 15-fold increase from 2019 figures in volunteer effort by 2030. Making it a compelling case for increasing carbon removal.</p>
<p><strong>The certification process lacks accuracy, transparency and accountability.</strong></p>
<p>The fact that there is no formal international standard for carbon offset accounting is at the foundation of most of the difficulty. Instead, commercial organisations such as Gold Standard, Verra, and the American Carbon Registry calculate, certify, and broker offsets using a mix of methodologies in each part of the process.</p>
<p>A <a href="https://www.compensate.com/articles/white-paper-qa/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">research paper</a> published in 2021 examined 100 offsets certified by Gold Standard and other organisations. Offsets from projects supporting forest conservation, climate-friendly farming, direct air capture technology, and other methods for reducing emissions. They discovered that 90% of the offsets either didn't offset as much as they claimed, aren't permanent, had negative consequences for local populations or ecosystems, or were a mix of the above.</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Bonus reason: current solutions are still building with web 2.0 methods.<br></strong>There is an opportunity to use the power of blockchain to make the exchange of carbon credits more efficient and transparent. That is why CARBEXC plans to combine DEFI, NFTs and the current carbon credit markets to make it easier to trade and burn carbon credits.</p>
<p class="align-left">If you want to be one of the first few to have access to our platform <a href="https://ejtx0zr7t56.typeform.com/to/VyP2ODz6" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">join our waitlist</a>.</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Why the world needs CARBEXC?</title>
        <author>
            <name>Kristof</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/why-the-world-needs-carbexc.html"/>
        <id>https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/why-the-world-needs-carbexc.html</id>

        <updated>2021-12-31T16:20:11+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Here are a few reasons why we believe that the world needs a solution like CARBEXC. The demand for carbon neutrality and Net-Zero solutions is exploding. Within the last two years, companies with accumulated annual revenue of +$10T have pledged carbon Net-Zero by 2040 -&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p class="msg msg--highlight ">Here are a few reasons why we believe that the world needs a solution like CARBEXC.</p>
<p><strong style="color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit;">The demand for carbon neutrality and Net-Zero solutions is exploding.</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Within the </span><i style="color: var(--text-editor-body-color); font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">last two years</i><span style="font-weight: 400;">, companies with accumulated annual revenue of +$10T have pledged carbon Net-Zero by 2040 - e.g. </span><a href="https://www.greenpeace.org/eastasia/press/7123/alibaba-pledges-carbon-neutrality-in-its-operations-by-2030-greenpeace-response/" style="font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">Alibaba</a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, </span><a href="https://www.theclimatepledge.com/us/en/Signatories" style="font-family: var(--font-base); font-size: inherit; font-weight: var(--font-weight-normal);">Amazon</a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, Microsoft, Reckitt, Infosys, Siemens, Unilever, Coca Cola, Heineken, IBM, IPG, Snap Inc, ASOS, Salesforce, P&amp;G, Accenture, Palo Networks, WPP, Klarna, Deloitte, Mercedes, Visa, Pepsico, Canva, Verizon, Uber to name a few of the 217+.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Carbon credits will conservatively become a <a href="https://www.google.com/url?q=https://katusaresearch.com/the-commodity-every-company-will-be-forced-to-buy/&amp;sa=D&amp;source=docs&amp;ust=1640877445275544&amp;usg=AOvVaw3it2khWkx9nCor8wPcBL0n" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">$160 billion market opportunity</a> according to Marin Katusa, Founder of Katusa Research, Fund Manager, best-selling author and world-renowned speculator.</span></p>
<p><strong>Governments are enforcing climate change actions. </strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The European Climate Law (July 2021) set a legally binding target of Net-Zero greenhouse gas emissions by 2050. The EU Institutions and the Member States are bound to take the necessary measures at EU and national level to meet the target (</span><a href="https://ec.europa.eu/clima/eu-action/european-green-deal/european-climate-law_en"><span style="font-weight: 400;">European Commision 2021</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">). The US is initiating similar steps (</span><a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/briefing-room/presidential-actions/2021/01/20/executive-order-protecting-public-health-and-environment-and-restoring-science-to-tackle-climate-crisis/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">The White House, January 2021</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">). China pledged to become carbon neutral before 2060 and boosted their pledge from 20% energy from renewables to 25% by 2030 (</span><a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/cop/china-submits-updated-climate-pledges-united-nations-2021-10-28/"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Reuters, October 2021</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">). India pledged Net-Zero carbon emissions by 2070 and their intentions of getting half its electricity from renewable sources by 2030 (</span><a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/world-asia-india-59125143"><span style="font-weight: 400;">BBC, November 2021</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">). And we’re only at the beginning.</span></p>
<p><strong>The competing solutions for contributing towards carbon solutions are limited.</strong></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Climate tech VC investments have increased 5x from 2016 to 2021 to only $32B (</span><a href="https://dealroom.co/uploaded/2021/10/Dealroom-London-and-Partners-Climate-Tech.pdf"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Dealroom, Oct 2021</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">). However, the current certification programs, supply and exchanges are not able to fulfil the demand of the market. </span></p>
<hr>
<p class="align-left">Those are a few reasons why we believe CARBEXC can be a game changer for this market and the world. If you want to join us on our mission and be one of the first few to have access to our platform join our waitlist <a href="https://ejtx0zr7t56.typeform.com/to/VyP2ODz6" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>How It Works</title>
        <author>
            <name>Kristof</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/how-it-works.html"/>
        <id>https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/how-it-works.html</id>

        <updated>2021-12-31T08:30:30+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Our platform is currently still being built and will be launched in Q3 of 2022, here is how it will work: Sign up: For your account and create your wallet Simply with passport and selfie. No credit card required. Buy: Carbon Credit spots and futures&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>Our platform is currently still being built and will be launched in Q3 of 2022, here is how it will work:</p>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Sign up: For your account and create your wallet</span>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="2"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Simply with passport and selfie. </span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="2"><span style="font-weight: 400;">No credit card required. </span></li>
</ol>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Buy: Carbon Credit spots and futures</span>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="2"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Discover carbon credit opportunities aligned with your goals</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="2"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Easy credit card or crypto checkout</span></li>
</ol>
</li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Share: Your carbon Net-Zero pledge</span>
<ol>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="2"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Share your results with your NFT certificates</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="2"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Motivate action around the world by leading the way</span></li>
</ol>
</li>
</ol>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>The Source Code</title>
        <author>
            <name>Kristof</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/the-source-code.html"/>
        <id>https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/the-source-code.html</id>

        <updated>2021-12-31T08:43:07+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/10/sourcecode.png" alt="" />
                    The Source Code is an incubator and accelerators that aims to be the conscious digital backbone for humanity. Our focus is on solving three major global issues: CLIMATE CHANGE Our planet is our only home. To take care of it is our utmost priority. Failing&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/10/sourcecode.png" alt="" />
                <p>The Source Code is an incubator and accelerators that aims to be the conscious digital backbone for humanity. Our focus is on solving three major global issues:</p>
<p><strong>CLIMATE CHANGE<br></strong><span style="font-weight: 400;">Our planet is our only home.  To take care of it is our utmost priority.  Failing to do so will end in catastrophe.</span></p>
<p><strong>THE INTERNET IS BROKEN<br></strong><span style="font-weight: 400;">We have become products for unsustainable,  unsecure and unreliable internet monopolies that steal our sovereignty.</span></p>
<p><strong>EDUCATION<br></strong><span style="font-weight: 400;">If we all had equal access to the same information and knowledge, those left behind would progress much faster.</span></p>
<p class="align-center">To learn more about The Source Code click here [ADD LINK TO WEBSITE]</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>For Carbon Credit Suppliers</title>
        <author>
            <name>Kristof</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/for-carbon-credit-suppliers.html"/>
        <id>https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/for-carbon-credit-suppliers.html</id>

        <updated>2021-12-31T08:24:30+02:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>For Investors</title>
        <author>
            <name>Kristof</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/for-investors.html"/>
        <id>https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/for-investors.html</id>

        <updated>2021-12-31T08:59:29+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    CARBEXC allows investors to easily access one of the best performing asset classes in the last three years while contributing to slowing down climate change. An exchange with endless opportunities. As an investor you can use CARBEXC to purchase Carbon Credits and Forwards, to trade&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p class="msg msg--highlight ">CARBEXC allows investors to easily access one of the best performing asset classes in the last three years while contributing to slowing down climate change.</p>
<p><em>An exchange with endless opportunities.</em></p>
<p>As an investor you can use CARBEXC to purchase Carbon Credits and Forwards, to trade them to companies directly on our exchange.</p>
<p> </p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--right"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/8/ipad-exchange.png" sizes="(min-width: 1260px) calc(3.22vw + 703px), (min-width: 900px) calc(50.59vw + 116px), (min-width: 840px) calc(5vw + 684px), calc(85.58vw + 23px)" srcset="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/8/responsive/ipad-exchange-xs.png 320w ,https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/8/responsive/ipad-exchange-sm.png 480w ,https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/8/responsive/ipad-exchange-md.png 768w"  alt="" width="525" height="662"></figure>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p>Access our exchange filled with useful <br>tools to make sound investment decisions.</p>
<p> </p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--right"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/8/exchange.png" sizes="(min-width: 1260px) calc(3.22vw + 703px), (min-width: 900px) calc(50.59vw + 116px), (min-width: 840px) calc(5vw + 684px), calc(85.58vw + 23px)" srcset="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/8/responsive/exchange-xs.png 320w ,https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/8/responsive/exchange-sm.png 480w ,https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/8/responsive/exchange-md.png 768w"  alt="" width="852" height="745"></figure>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p>Store your Carbon Credits or Forwards on our mobile self-custodial digital wallet</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>For Companies</title>
        <author>
            <name>Kristof</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/for-companie.html"/>
        <id>https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/for-companie.html</id>

        <updated>2021-12-30T15:26:00+02:00</updated>
            <summary></summary>
        <content></content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Carbon Forwards</title>
        <author>
            <name>Kristof</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/carbon-futures.html"/>
        <id>https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/carbon-futures.html</id>

        <updated>2021-12-31T16:04:42+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Carbon Forwards is a visionary new asset class for the Voluntary Carbon Markets (VCM), that enable companies to buy carbon credits of future carbon removal projects. Our focus on carbon removal projects is to increase the impact we have on slowing down climate change. To&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p class="msg msg--highlight "><em>Carbon Forwards</em> is a visionary new asset class for the Voluntary Carbon Markets (VCM), that enable companies to buy carbon credits of future carbon removal projects. Our focus on carbon removal projects is to increase the impact we have on slowing down climate change.</p>
<p>To create Carbon Forwards CARBEXC has developed partnerships and is developing a unique certification process that involves satellite imagery, drones and IoT devices to track the projects.</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Providing ROI while funding carbon removal projects.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Buy, sell and trade carbon credit futures and help organizations making an impact towards the betterment of our planet and our species with high impact nature-based solutions.</span></p>
<p><i><span style="font-weight: 400;">Not just reducing carbon emissions. No - that’s cutting corners and isn’t enough. We catalyze carbon removal projects, to remove carbon out of the atmosphere for 2x impact.</span></i></p>
<p><strong>PARTNERSHIPS<br></strong><strong><span style="font-weight: 400;">We are partnering with leaders of carbon removal projects and are always looking for new partners.</span></strong></p>
<p><strong>Mangroves Blue Carbon with Vlinder</strong></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--left"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/6/vlinder.png" sizes="(min-width: 1260px) calc(3.22vw + 703px), (min-width: 900px) calc(50.59vw + 116px), (min-width: 840px) calc(5vw + 684px), calc(85.58vw + 23px)" srcset="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/6/responsive/vlinder-xs.png 320w ,https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/6/responsive/vlinder-sm.png 480w ,https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/6/responsive/vlinder-md.png 768w"  alt="" width="251" height="70"></figure>
<p>Mangrove forests sequester up to five times more carbon dioxide from the atmosphere than other types of forest.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Hemp Green Carbon with Signara Global Solutions</strong></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--left"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/6/signara-2.png" sizes="(min-width: 1260px) calc(3.22vw + 703px), (min-width: 900px) calc(50.59vw + 116px), (min-width: 840px) calc(5vw + 684px), calc(85.58vw + 23px)" srcset="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/6/responsive/signara-2-xs.png 320w ,https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/6/responsive/signara-2-sm.png 480w ,https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/6/responsive/signara-2-md.png 768w"  alt="" width="246" height="121"></figure>
<p><br>Hemp is one of the fastest converting CO2-to-biomass tools available today; proved more efficient than agro-forestry (European Industrial Hemp Association)</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Educating Children with </strong><strong>Take Action Global</strong></p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--left"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/6/tag.png" sizes="(min-width: 1260px) calc(3.22vw + 703px), (min-width: 900px) calc(50.59vw + 116px), (min-width: 840px) calc(5vw + 684px), calc(85.58vw + 23px)" srcset="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/6/responsive/tag-xs.png 320w ,https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/6/responsive/tag-sm.png 480w ,https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/6/responsive/tag-md.png 768w"  alt="" width="222" height="94"></figure>
<p><br>Over two million children are earning carbon credits by learning and then teaching about harvesting carbon.</p>
<p> </p>
<hr>
<p class="align-center">Are you a potential supplier of carbon credits.</p>
<p class="align-center"><a href="#INTERNAL_LINK#/post/null" title="https://ejtx0zr7t56.typeform.com/to/VyP2ODz6">Join Our Waitlist</a></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Carbon Exchange</title>
        <author>
            <name>Kristof</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/carbon-exchange.html"/>
        <id>https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/carbon-exchange.html</id>

        <updated>2022-01-05T10:34:20+02:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     A Carbon Credit Exchange solution with a digital wallet, carbon credit tokens and a marketplace webshop. Since day one our missions has been to use the power of Decentralized Finance (DEFI) to empower everyone to save our planet. 1 - Trustworthy 2 - Easy&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/5/CEXAsset-11.png" sizes="(min-width: 1260px) calc(3.22vw + 703px), (min-width: 900px) calc(50.59vw + 116px), (min-width: 840px) calc(5vw + 684px), calc(85.58vw + 23px)" srcset="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/5/responsive/CEXAsset-11-xs.png 320w ,https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/5/responsive/CEXAsset-11-sm.png 480w ,https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/5/responsive/CEXAsset-11-md.png 768w"  alt="" width="4000" height="1888"></figure>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">A Carbon Credit Exchange solution with a digital wallet, carbon credit tokens and a marketplace webshop. </span></p>
<p>Since day one our missions has been to use the power of Decentralized Finance (DEFI) to empower everyone to save our planet.</p>
<table style="border-collapse: collapse; width: 100%;" border="1">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td style="width: 33.3333%;">
<p><strong>1 - Trustworthy</strong></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Tokenized carbon credits</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Blockchain-based settlement</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Non-custodial mobile wallet and client side bidding</span></li>
</ul>
</td>
<td style="width: 33.3333%;">
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;"><strong>2 - Easy and accessible</strong></span></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Fast credit card checkout</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Instant settlement</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Transferable &amp; tradable digital token</span></li>
</ul>
</td>
<td style="width: 33.3333%;">
<p><strong>3 - Quality and Impact</strong></p>
<ul>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">CARBEXC certified carbon credit forwards</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">All VCS-certified carbon credits</span></li>
<li style="font-weight: 400;" aria-level="1"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Carbon credit offset on demand</span></li>
</ul>
</td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<h2>Exchange Platform</h2>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/5/CEXAsset-19.png" sizes="(min-width: 1260px) calc(3.22vw + 703px), (min-width: 900px) calc(50.59vw + 116px), (min-width: 840px) calc(5vw + 684px), calc(85.58vw + 23px)" srcset="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/5/responsive/CEXAsset-19-xs.png 320w ,https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/5/responsive/CEXAsset-19-sm.png 480w ,https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/5/responsive/CEXAsset-19-md.png 768w"  alt="" width="560" height="592"></figure>
<p>Our simple exchange interface allows anyone to easily understand and participate in the exchange of carbon credits and futures.</p>
<h2>Digital Wallet</h2>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/5/CEXAsset-15-2.png" sizes="(min-width: 1260px) calc(3.22vw + 703px), (min-width: 900px) calc(50.59vw + 116px), (min-width: 840px) calc(5vw + 684px), calc(85.58vw + 23px)" srcset="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/5/responsive/CEXAsset-15-2-xs.png 320w ,https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/5/responsive/CEXAsset-15-2-sm.png 480w ,https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/5/responsive/CEXAsset-15-2-md.png 768w"  alt="" width="582" height="521"></figure>
<p>Store all your carbon credits or forwards on our non-custodial digital wallet.</p>
<h2>Marketplace Webshop</h2>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/5/desktop-exchange-3.png" sizes="(min-width: 1260px) calc(3.22vw + 703px), (min-width: 900px) calc(50.59vw + 116px), (min-width: 840px) calc(5vw + 684px), calc(85.58vw + 23px)" srcset="https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/5/responsive/desktop-exchange-3-xs.png 320w ,https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/5/responsive/desktop-exchange-3-sm.png 480w ,https://carbexc.github.io/www_carbexc/media/posts/5/responsive/desktop-exchange-3-md.png 768w"  alt="" width="594" height="343"></figure>
<p>Discover new carbon removal projects without having to understand anything about crypto or blockchain and check-out using Credit card, Apple Pay, SEPA or SWIFT.</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
